<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<hpcportal:resources xmlns="http://www.platform.com/2008"
	xmlns:hpcportal="http://www.platform.com/2008/hpcportal/schema"
	xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
	xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.platform.com/2008/hpcportal/schema resources.xsd">
	<hpcportal:resource name="EGOClusterReportname">Cluster Availability - EGO</hpcportal:resource>
	<hpcportal:resource name="EGOClusterSummary">EGO host availability in a cluster.</hpcportal:resource>
	<hpcportal:resource name="EGOClusterDescription"><![CDATA[
	                <h3>Purpose</h3>
			 <ul type="disc">
			<li>This report allows you to see host availability in an EGO cluster.</li>
			</ul>
	            <h3>Data Description</h3>
	            <ul type="disc">
	            <li>This report displays the number of hosts in each host state within the specified period of time.</li>
	           <li>The host states are:
	           <br> - OK: The host is ready for allocation and execution.
	           <br> - Unavailable: The load index collector is unavailable.
	           <br> - Closed: The host is closed by the administrator or the load thresholds have been reached.
	           </li>
	           </ul>
	          <h3>Analysis</h3>
	          <ul type="disc">
	          <li>Confirm that the cluster availability is acceptable, and identify any time periods for when the cluster is unavailable.</li>
	          <li>Identify hosts with the "closed","unavail" state.
	          <br> - Hosts with "closed" status are not available for scheduling.
	          <br> - Hosts with "unavail" status might be down, or the LIM and PEM on the host are unreachable.
	          </li>
	         </ul>
		]]></hpcportal:resource>
	 <hpcportal:resource name="EGOClusterCategory">EGO</hpcportal:resource>
	 <hpcportal:resource name="EGOClusterAttribute">Cluster</hpcportal:resource>
	 <hpcportal:resource name="HostResourceName">Host Resource Usage</hpcportal:resource>
	 <hpcportal:resource name="HostResourceSummary">Resource usage trends for selected hosts.</hpcportal:resource>
	 <hpcportal:resource name="HostResourceDescription"><![CDATA[
	 	  <ul>
     <li style="line-height:20px;">Purpose</li>
	 <li style="font-weight:normal;line-height:20px;text-indent:20px;">This report allows you to identify resource usage trends for selected hosts over time.</li>
	 
     <li style="line-height:20px;">Data Description</li>
	 <li style="font-weight:normal;line-height:20px;text-indent:20px;">Displays the amount of resources that selected hosts used over the specified period of time, according to a specified resource metric.</li>
	  <li style="font-weight:normal;line-height:20px;text-indent:20px;">You can select the resource metric from 11 internal indices or from the external indices as defined by elim.</li>
	 
      <li style="line-height: 20px;">Analysis</li>
	 <li style="font-weight:normal;line-height:20px;text-indent:20px;">Find resource utilization trends for selected hosts and determine whether the hosts are fully utilizing their resources.</li>
	</ul>]]></hpcportal:resource>
	<hpcportal:resource name="HostAttribute">Cluster</hpcportal:resource>
	<hpcportal:resource name="Host">Host</hpcportal:resource>
	<hpcportal:resource name="HostMetric">Metric</hpcportal:resource>

	 <hpcportal:resource name="RVARP">Resource Allocation vs Resource Plan</hpcportal:resource>
	 <hpcportal:resource name="RVARPSummary">Actual resource allocation compared to resource plan and unsatisfied resource demand for the selected consumer.</hpcportal:resource>
	 <hpcportal:resource name="RVARPDescription">
	 <![CDATA[
	    <h3>Purpose</h3>
	      <ul type="disc">
	       <li>This report allows you to compare the actual resource allocation with the resource plan and unsatisfied resource demand. This report also allows you to identify the trends in how the resource is allocated to the EGO consumer.</li>
	        </ul>
	        <h3>Data Description</h3>
	       <ul type="disc">
	      <li>This report displays the number of allocated slots, planned slots (according to policy), and the number of requested slots.</li>
	       </ul>
	       <h3>Analysis</h3>
	       <ul type="disc">
	      <li>Determine whether the resources have been allocated properly according to demand.</li>
	    <li>Identify the trend in resources allocated to the consumer.</li>
	     </ul>
	     <h3>Best Practices</h3>
	    <ul type="disc">
	   <li>If the resources are not allocated according to demand, adjust your allocation policy to optimize the resource usage.</li>
	   </ul>]]>
	 </hpcportal:resource>
 <hpcportal:resource name="RVARPConsumer">Consumer</hpcportal:resource>
 <hpcportal:resource name="RVARPCluster">Cluster</hpcportal:resource>
 <hpcportal:resource name="RVARPY"># of slots</hpcportal:resource>

  <hpcportal:resource name="ActiveJobName">Active Job States Statistics by Queue</hpcportal:resource>
  <hpcportal:resource name="ActiveJobSummary">Number of active jobs in each active job state in a selected queue</hpcportal:resource>
  <hpcportal:resource name="ActiveJobDescription">
  <![CDATA[
	 <ul>
	  <li style="line-height:20px;">Purpose</li>
	  <li style="font-weight:normal;line-height:20px;text-indent:20px;">This report allows you to identify the trends in the number of jobs in each active job state in a single queue within the specified period of time.</li>
	  <li style="line-height:20px;">Data Description</li>
	  <li style="font-weight:normal;line-height:20px;text-indent:20px;">This report displays the number of jobs in each job state at the sampling point (every five minutes).</li>
	  <li style="font-weight:normal;line-height:20px;text-indent:20px;">The job states are: <br>
	    - PEND: Waiting in a queue for scheduling and dispatch. <br>
	    - RUN: Dispatched to a host and running. <br>
	    - PSUSP: Suspended while pending. <br>
	    - USUSP: Suspended by user. <br>
	    - SSUSP: Suspended by the LSF system. <br>
	    - WAIT: Members of a chunk job that are waiting to run.</li>
	  <li style="line-height:20px;">Analysis</li>
	  <li style="font-weight:normal;line-height:20px;text-indent:20px;">Compare the number of pending jobs with the number of running jobs: <br>
	    - If there is an increase in the number of pending jobs during the specified time period while the number of running jobs is stable, your queue may have reached its slot limit. <br>
	    - If there is a decrease in the number of pending jobs and running jobs, this indicates that the workload is low.</li>
	  <li style="font-weight:normal;line-height:20px;text-indent:20px;">Determine if the queue has a large increase in the number of pending jobs.</li>
	  <li style="line-height:20px;">Best Practices</li>
	  <li style="font-weight:normal;line-height:20px;text-indent:20px;">If the queue has a large increase in the number of pending jobs, examine the jobs' pending reasons on that queue.</li>
	  <li style="font-weight:normal;line-height:20px;text-indent:20px;">Compare the number of jobs in multiple queues by producing a different report for each queue.
	    - Identify whether a specific queue has an irregular number of suspended jobs (perhaps due to queue configuration) by comparing the number of suspended jobs in a preemptable queue with the number of jobs in a preemptive queue.</li>
	</ul>
  ]]>
  </hpcportal:resource>
  <hpcportal:resource name="HostResource">resource</hpcportal:resource>
   <hpcportal:resource name="ActiveJobCategory">LSF</hpcportal:resource>
    <hpcportal:resource name="ActiveJobQueue">QUEUE</hpcportal:resource>
    <hpcportal:resource name="ActiveX">TIME_STAMP</hpcportal:resource>
    <hpcportal:resource name="ActiveY"># of jobs in each state</hpcportal:resource>
    <hpcportal:resource name="ActiveYHost"># of hosts in each state</hpcportal:resource>
    <hpcportal:resource name="ActiveYnumOfJobInState"># of jobs in each state</hpcportal:resource>
    <hpcportal:resource name="LicenseUsgeName">License Usage</hpcportal:resource>
    <hpcportal:resource name="LicenseUsgeSummary">The license usage under License Scheduler. You can only produce this report if you use LSF License Scheduler.</hpcportal:resource>
     <hpcportal:resource name="LicenseUsgeCategory">LSF License Scheduler</hpcportal:resource>
     <hpcportal:resource name="LicenseUsgeDescription">
      <![CDATA[      
      <ul>
		  <li style="line-height:20px;">Purpose</li>
		  <li style="line-height:20px; font-weight:normal; text-indent : 20px;">This report allows you to examine the license usage of a license feature. </li>
		  <li style="line-height:20px;">Data Description</li>
		  <li style="font-weight:normal;line-height:20px;text-indent:20px;">This report displays the number of licenses used over a specified period of time. You can filter your report by selecting the following license usage parameters:
          <br>- License usage: The usage state of your license.
         <br>- License feature: The license feature you want to examine.
      <br>- License service domain: The service domain for this report.
       <br>- Projects: Specific projects to which the license is assigned. You may select up to ten projects for your report.
         </li>
		  <li style="line-height:20px;">Analysis</li>
		  <li style="font-weight:normal;line-height:20px;text-indent:20px;">Identify the trends in license usage to see whether the license usage for a particular license feature is optimal.</li>
		  <li style="line-height:20px;">Best Practices</li>
		  <li style="font-weight:normal;line-height:20px;text-indent:20px;">If license usage is not optimal, change the number of licenses to suit your needs.</li>
		</ul>
       ]]>
     </hpcportal:resource>
     <hpcportal:resource name="LicenseUsgeFeatureName">Feature Name</hpcportal:resource>
     <hpcportal:resource name="LicenseUsgeDomainName">Domain Name</hpcportal:resource>
     <hpcportal:resource name="LicenseUsgeProjectName">Project Name</hpcportal:resource>
     <hpcportal:resource name="LicenseUsge">Usage</hpcportal:resource>
      <hpcportal:resource name="LicenseUsgeTitle">The usage of license</hpcportal:resource>
      <hpcportal:resource name="LicenseUsgeTitle2">on service domain</hpcportal:resource>
      <hpcportal:resource name="LicenseUsgeY"># of license</hpcportal:resource>
     <hpcportal:resource name="LicenseUsged">used</hpcportal:resource> 
     <hpcportal:resource name="LicenseAllocated">allocated</hpcportal:resource> 
     <hpcportal:resource name="LicenseFreed">freed</hpcportal:resource> 
      
     
     
     <hpcportal:resource name="LSFClusterName">Cluster Availability - LSF</hpcportal:resource>
     
     <hpcportal:resource name="CLUSTER NAME">Cluster Name</hpcportal:resource>
     <hpcportal:resource name="From">From</hpcportal:resource>
     <hpcportal:resource name="to">to</hpcportal:resource>
  
     <hpcportal:resource name="LSFClusterSummary">LSF host availability in a LSF cluster.</hpcportal:resource>
     <hpcportal:resource name="LSFClusterDescription">
     <![CDATA[
       <ul>
		  <li style="line-height:20px;">Purpose</li>
		  <li style="font-weight:normal;line-height:20px;text-indent:20px;">This report allows you to see the LSF host availability in a LSF cluster over time.</li>
		  <li style="line-height:20px;">Data Description</li>
		  <li style="font-weight:normal;line-height:20px;text-indent:20px;">This report displays the number of hosts in each host state within the specified period of time. The status of each host is taken directly from bhosts.</li>
		  <li style="font-weight:normal;line-height:20px;text-indent:20px;">The host states are: <br>
		    - OK: The host is available to accept jobs. <br>
		    - Unavail: Either the host is unreachable or the LIM is down. <br>
		    - Unreach: The LIM on the host is running, but sbatchd is down. <br>
		    - Closed: The host is not allowed to accept any remote batch jobs. There are several reasons for the host to be closed. </li>
		  <li style="line-height:20px;">Analysis</li>
		  <li style="font-weight:normal;line-height:20px;text-indent:20px;">Use this report to confirm that the host availability is acceptable, and to identify any time periods where hosts are unavailable.</li>
		  
		</ul>        
	           ]]>
     </hpcportal:resource>
      <hpcportal:resource name="LSFCluster">Cluster</hpcportal:resource>

      <hpcportal:resource name="ClusterJobHourlyName">Cluster Job Hourly Throughput</hpcportal:resource>
      <hpcportal:resource name="ClusterJobHourlySummary">Number of submitted, exited, and done jobs in a cluster.</hpcportal:resource>
      <hpcportal:resource name="ClusterJobHourlyDescription">
      <![CDATA[
	     <ul>
		  <li style="line-height:20px;">Purpose</li>
		  <li style="font-weight:normal;line-height:20px;text-indent:20px;">This report allows you to monitor cluster throughput trends over time to confirm that jobs are running properly in a cluster.</li>
		  <li style="line-height:20px;">Data Description</li>
		  <li style="font-weight:normal;line-height:20px;text-indent:20px;">This report displays the number of jobs that are submitted, exited, and done at each hour within a specified period of time in the cluster. This report displays the following data: <br>
		    - Number of submitted jobs. <br>
		    - Number of exited jobs: jobs that were not successfully dispatched or completed with an error code (that is, with a non-zero exit code). <br>
		    - Number of done jobs: jobs that were successfully dispatched and completed without an error (that is, with a zero exit code). </li>
		  <li style="line-height:20px;">Analysis</li>
		  <li style="font-weight:normal;line-height:20px;text-indent:20px;">Compare the number of done jobs with the number of submitted jobs: <br>
		    - If the numbers are always similar, there is no change in the way the typical job passes through the system. <br>
		    - If the number of submitted jobs increases and the number of done jobs becomes constant, the cluster may have reached maximum capacity, causing longer wait times for jobs to start. </li>
		  <li style="font-weight:normal;line-height:20px;text-indent:20px;">If a number of jobs are submitted but no jobs are done during the specified period, you may have some long-running jobs within this period.</li>
		  <li style="font-weight:normal;line-height:20px;text-indent:20px;">Look at trends in the submitted and done jobs. If the chart looks flat within the specified period, your cluster is performing well and is stable.</li>
		  <li style="font-weight:normal;line-height:20px;text-indent:20px;">Note the time of any exited jobs.</li>
		</ul>
	]]>
      </hpcportal:resource>
     <hpcportal:resource name="ClusterJobHourly">Cluster</hpcportal:resource> 

      <hpcportal:resource name="ClusterJobSlotName">Cluster Job Slot Utilization</hpcportal:resource>
      <hpcportal:resource name="ClusterJobSlotSummary">Job slot utilization levels in your cluster.</hpcportal:resource>
      <hpcportal:resource name="ClusterSlotUtilX">TIME STAMP</hpcportal:resource>
      <hpcportal:resource name="ClusterSlotUtilY">Job Slot Utilization(%)</hpcportal:resource>
      <hpcportal:resource name="ClusterJobSlotDescription">
      <![CDATA[
         <ul>
		  <li style="line-height:20px;">Purpose</li>
		  <li style="line-height:20px; font-weight:normal; text-indent : 20px;">This report allows you to identify the following: <br>
		    -  The hours when job slots are under-utilized. <br>
		    -  The duration of peak utilization and time patterns of occurrence. <br>
		    -  The spare resource capacity of your cluster. </li>
		  <li style="line-height:20px;">Data Description</li>
		  <li style="font-weight:normal;line-height:20px;text-indent:20px;">This report shows the cluster-wide job slot utilization over a period of time. Cluster Job Slot Utilization = (Maximum # of job slots used within the hour) / (total job slots available).</li>
		  <li style="line-height:20px;">Analysis</li>
		  <li style="font-weight:normal;line-height:20px;text-indent:20px;">Find the time periods that job slots were underutilized. Identify any patterns of job slot utilization. If the slot utilization is low while the number of running jobs in one of your queues is decreasing (consult the Active Job States Statistics by Queue report), your cluster workload is low. </li>
		</ul>
  ]]>
      </hpcportal:resource>
       <hpcportal:resource name="ClusterJobSlotCluster">Cluster</hpcportal:resource>

        <hpcportal:resource name="JobsForwardedName">Jobs Forwarded to Other Clusters</hpcportal:resource>
        <hpcportal:resource name="JobsForwardedSummary">The number of jobs forwarded from your cluster to other clusters. You can only produce this report if you use LSF MultiCluster.</hpcportal:resource>
	<hpcportal:resource name="JobsForwardedCategory">LSF MultiCluster</hpcportal:resource>
	 <hpcportal:resource name="JobsForwardedDescription">
	 <![CDATA[            
            <ul>
		  	 <li style="line-height:20px;">Purpose</li>
		  	 <li style="font-weight:normal;line-height:20px;text-indent:20px;">This report allows you to compare the quantity of jobs forwarded to different clusters and to identify the trends of job forwarding.</li>
		 	 <li style="line-height:20px;">Data Description</li>
		 	 <li style="font-weight:normal;line-height:20px;text-indent:20px;">This report shows the number of forwarded jobs to other clusters at each hour over time.</li>
		 	 <li style="font-weight:normal;line-height:20px;text-indent:20px;">This report is used with LSF MultiCluster.</li>
		 	 <li style="line-height:20px;">Analysis</li>
		 	 <li style="font-weight:normal;line-height:20px;text-indent:20px;">Identify the cluster where your cluster is forwarding the most jobs: this cluster may have more resource capacity.</li>
		 	 <li style="font-weight:normal;line-height:20px;text-indent:20px;">For periods when your cluster is forwarding a large number of jobs, check whether your users are submitting jobs to be run on a remote cluster. If not, your cluster is starving for resources (all local hosts in your cluster are busy).</li>
		 	 <li style="line-height:20px;">Best Practices</li>
		 	 <li style="font-weight:normal;line-height:20px;text-indent:20px;">If your cluster is starving for resources, expand your cluster so it has more hosts or resources.</li>
			</ul>
            
            ]]>
	 </hpcportal:resource>
	  <hpcportal:resource name="JobsForwardedCluster">Cluster</hpcportal:resource>
	  <hpcportal:resource name="JobsForwardedY"># of jobs</hpcportal:resource>

	   <hpcportal:resource name="JobSlotUsageName">Job Slot Usage by Application Tag</hpcportal:resource>
	   <hpcportal:resource name="JobSlotUsageSummary">Job slots used by applications as indicated by the application tag</hpcportal:resource>
	   <hpcportal:resource name="JobSlotUsageDescription">
	   <![CDATA[	           
	            <ul>
		  	 <li style="line-height:20px;">Purpose</li>
		  	 <li style="font-weight:normal;line-height:20px;text-indent:20px;">This report shows how job slots are used by the application tag.</li>
		 	 <li style="line-height:20px;">Data Description</li>
		 	 <li style="font-weight:normal;line-height:20px;text-indent:20px;">This report displays the number of job slots used by the selected application tags over the specified period of time.</li>
		 	 <li style="font-weight:normal;line-height:20px;text-indent:20px;">This report is used with application tag profile configuration in LSF.</li>
		 	 <li style="line-height:20px;">Analysis</li>
		 	 <li style="font-weight:normal;line-height:20px;text-indent:20px;">Determine job slot usage trends over time.</li>
		 	 <li style="font-weight:normal;line-height:20px;text-indent:20px;">Identify the time of peak usage in the report.</li>
		 	 <li style="font-weight:normal;line-height:20px;text-indent:20px;">Identify the number of job slots used by the application tag at each sampling point.</li>
		 	 <li style="font-weight:normal;line-height:20px;text-indent:20px;">Compare the job slot usage of different application tags</li>
			</ul>
	   ]]>
	   </hpcportal:resource>
 <hpcportal:resource name="JobSlotUsageApplication">Application</hpcportal:resource>
 <hpcportal:resource name="JobSlotUsageY"># of job slots used</hpcportal:resource>
 
  <hpcportal:resource name="JobsReceivedName">Jobs Received from Other Clusters</hpcportal:resource>
  <hpcportal:resource name="JobsReceivedSummary">The number of jobs forwarded to your cluster from other clusters. You can only produce this report if you use LSF MultiCluster.</hpcportal:resource>
   <hpcportal:resource name="JobsReceivedDescription">
   <![CDATA[              
            <ul>
		  	 <li style="line-height:20px;">Purpose</li>
		  	 <li style="font-weight:normal;line-height:20px;text-indent:20px;">This report allows you to compare the quantity of jobs received from other clusters.</li>
		 	 <li style="line-height:20px;">Data Description</li>
		 	 <li style="font-weight:normal;line-height:20px;text-indent:20px;">This report shows the number of received jobs from other clusters at each hour.</li>
		 	 <li style="font-weight:normal;line-height:20px;text-indent:20px;">This report is used with LSF MultiCluster.</li>
		 	 <li style="line-height:20px;">Analysis</li>
		 	 <li style="font-weight:normal;line-height:20px;text-indent:20px;">For periods when your cluster is receiving a large number of jobs from a particular cluster, check whether the users of the forwarding cluster are submitting jobs to be run on your cluster. If not, either the forwarding cluster is starving for resources (all local hosts in the forwarding cluster are busy).</li>
		 	 <li style="line-height:20px;">Best Practices</li>
		 	 <li style="font-weight:normal;line-height:20px;text-indent:20px;">If the forwarding cluster is starving for resources, expand the forwarding cluster so it has more hosts or resources.</li>
			</ul>
              
              ]]>
   </hpcportal:resource> 
 <hpcportal:resource name="JobsReceivedCluster">Cluster</hpcportal:resource>  

 <hpcportal:resource name="LSFPerformanceMetricName">Performance Metrics</hpcportal:resource>
 <hpcportal:resource name="LSFPerformanceMetricSummary">Internal performance metrics trend for a cluster.</hpcportal:resource>
 <hpcportal:resource name="LSFPerformanceMetricDescription">
  <![CDATA[ 
  			<ul>
		  	 <li style="line-height:20px;">Purpose</li>
		  	 <li style="font-weight:normal;line-height:20px;text-indent:20px;">This report allows you to identify internal performance metrics trend for your cluster over time.</li>
		 	 <li style="line-height:20px;">Data Description</li>
		 	 <li style="font-weight:normal;line-height:20px;text-indent:20px;">This report displays selected performance metrics over the specified period of time.</li>
		 	 <li style="line-height:20px;">Analysis</li>
		 	 <li style="font-weight:normal;line-height:20px;text-indent:20px;">Use the performance metrics trend for the cluster to determine whether the cluster is running at optimum performance. For example, if the number of dispatched jobs compared to the number of slots in the system is low, your cluster is not running at optimum performance.</li>
			</ul>
     ]]>
 </hpcportal:resource>
 <hpcportal:resource name="LSFPerformanceMetricQuery">Query Selection</hpcportal:resource>
  <hpcportal:resource name="LSFPerformanceMetricCluster">Cluster</hpcportal:resource>
  <hpcportal:resource name="LSFPerformanceMetricTotalQuery">Total Query</hpcportal:resource>
  <hpcportal:resource name="LSFPerformanceMetricJobQuery">Job Query</hpcportal:resource>
  <hpcportal:resource name="LSFPerformanceMetricQueueQuery">Queue Query</hpcportal:resource>
  <hpcportal:resource name="LSFPerformanceMetricHostQuery">Host Query</hpcportal:resource>
  <hpcportal:resource name="LSFPerformanceMetricSubmissionRequest">Submission Request</hpcportal:resource>
  <hpcportal:resource name="LSFPerformanceMetricJobSubmitted">Job Submitted</hpcportal:resource>
  <hpcportal:resource name="LSFPerformanceMetricJobDispatched">Job Dispatched</hpcportal:resource>
  <hpcportal:resource name="LSFPerformanceMetricJobCompleted">Job Completed</hpcportal:resource>
  <hpcportal:resource name="LSFPerformanceMetricJobMCSent">Job MC Sent</hpcportal:resource>
  <hpcportal:resource name="LSFPerformanceMetricJobMCReceived">Job MC Received</hpcportal:resource>

  
 <hpcportal:resource name="ServiceLevelAgreementName">Service Level Agreement (SLA)</hpcportal:resource>
 <hpcportal:resource name="ServiceLevelAgreementSummary">Job statistics by job state over time, compared with SLA goals.</hpcportal:resource>
 <hpcportal:resource name="ServiceLevelAgreementDescription">
 <![CDATA[  
            <ul>
		  	 <li style="line-height:20px;">Purpose</li>
		  	 <li style="font-weight:normal;line-height:20px;text-indent:20px;">This report allows you to compare your job completion statistics with pre-defined SLA goals.</li>
		 	 <li style="line-height:20px;">Data Description</li>
		 	 <li style="font-weight:normal;line-height:20px;text-indent:20px;">This report displays number of jobs in each job state over the specified period of time.</li>
		 	 <li style="font-weight:normal;line-height:20px;text-indent:20px;">In the <Strong>SLA Name</Strong> field, select a pre-defined SLA class with which to compare your job statistics.</li>
		 	 <li style="line-height:20px;">Analysis</li>
		 	 <li style="font-weight:normal;line-height:20px;text-indent:20px;">Compare the number of jobs with the SLA goals:
          <br> - If the number of jobs consistently exceeds the SLA goals, your SLA is satisfied.
           <br >- If the number of jobs is consistently much less than the SLA goals, your SLA has not been satisfied.</li>
		 	 <li style="line-height:20px;">Best Practices</li>
		 	 <li style="font-weight:normal;line-height:20px;text-indent:20px;">If your SLA is consistently unsatisfied, you should increase the resources in your cluster.</li>
			</ul>
 ]]>
 </hpcportal:resource>
 <hpcportal:resource name="ServiceLevelAgreementSLAName">Service Level Agreement (SLA)</hpcportal:resource>
  <hpcportal:resource name="ServiceLevelAgreementCluster">Cluster</hpcportal:resource>
	<hpcportal:resource name="Metric">Metric</hpcportal:resource>
	
	<hpcportal:resource name="TimeOfDay">Time of Day</hpcportal:resource>
	<hpcportal:resource name="DayOfMonth">Day of Month</hpcportal:resource>
	<hpcportal:resource name="Legend">Legend</hpcportal:resource>
	<hpcportal:resource name="NumOf"># of</hpcportal:resource>
	
<hpcportal:resource name="AverageJobPendingName">Average Job Pending Time by Queue</hpcportal:resource>
	   <hpcportal:resource name="AverageJobPendingSummary">Average pending time of all jobs in PEND state of a selected queue</hpcportal:resource>
	   <hpcportal:resource name="AverageJobPendingDescription">
	   <![CDATA[
	    <ul>
		  <li style="line-height:20px;">Purpose</li>
		  <li style="font-weight:normal;line-height:20px;text-indent:20px;">This report allows you to identify patterns of jobs waiting in a single queue within the specified period of time.</li>
		  <li style="line-height:20px;">Data Description</li>
		  <li style="font-weight:normal;line-height:20px;text-indent:20px;">This report displays the average pending time of all jobs in PEND state of a selected queue at each sampling point (every five minutes, by default).</li>
		  <li style="line-height:20px;">Analysis</li>
		  <li style="font-weight:normal;line-height:20px;text-indent:20px;">If the queue has a big average pending time, examine the jobs’ pending reasons for that queue and check whether there are suspended jobs while pending in the queue.</li>
		  <li style="font-weight:normal;line-height:20px;text-indent:20px;">Compare this report with “Active Job States Statistics by Queue” report to check whether any jobs from this queue are running within the same period.</li>
		</ul>
	   ]]>
	   </hpcportal:resource>
	   <hpcportal:resource name="AverageJobPendingCategory">LSF</hpcportal:resource>
 <hpcportal:resource name="AverageJobPendingX">TIME_STAMP</hpcportal:resource>
 <hpcportal:resource name="AverageJobPendingY">Average Job Pending Time(minutes)</hpcportal:resource>
 
 <hpcportal:resource name="LicenseFreeNumTitle">The free number of license feature</hpcportal:resource>
 <hpcportal:resource name="LicenseFreeNumReportName">Free Licenses</hpcportal:resource>
 <hpcportal:resource name="LicenseFreeNumSummary">The free number of license feature over period of time</hpcportal:resource>
 <hpcportal:resource name="LicenseFreeNumDescription">
 	<![CDATA[
 	 <ul>
      <li style="line-height: 20px;">Purpose</li>
	  <li style="font-weight: normal; line-height: 20px; text-indent : 20px;">This report allows you to see the free license number for selected features over time.</li>
      <li style="line-height: 20px;">Data Description</li>
	  <li style="font-weight: normal; line-height: 20px; text-indent : 20px;">This report displays the free license number that selected feature over the specified period of time.</li>
	  <li style="font-weight: normal; line-height: 20px; text-indent : 20px;">You can choose one or more features for generate report. A maximum of selected feature is 10.</li>
      <li style="line-height: 20px;">Analysis</li>
	  <li style="font-weight: normal; line-height: 20px; text-indent : 20px;">Find the free license number that you selected features. And let you know feature usage of license.</li>
	</ul>
 	]]>
 </hpcportal:resource>
</hpcportal:resources>
